{
  "questions": [
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{\\frac{8}{9}}{\\frac{4}{2}}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{0}{1}",
        "\\frac{31}{90}",
        "\\frac{4}{9}",
        "\\frac{26}{9}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{4}{9}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionDivision.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_dividera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{\\frac{4}{3}}{\\frac{6}{2}}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{31}{90}",
        "\\frac{13}{3}",
        "\\frac{4}{1}",
        "\\frac{4}{9}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{4}{9}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionDivision.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_dividera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{\\frac{7}{4}}{\\frac{1}{6}}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{7}{24}",
        "\\frac{0}{1}",
        "\\frac{23}{12}",
        "\\frac{21}{2}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{21}{2}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionDivision.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_dividera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{\\frac{10}{3}}{\\frac{2}{1}}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{16}{3}",
        "\\frac{20}{3}",
        "\\frac{5}{3}",
        "\\frac{3}{2}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{5}{3}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionDivision.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_dividera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{8}{5} \\cdot \\frac{5}{2}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{4}{1}",
        "\\frac{2}{1}",
        "\\frac{41}{10}",
        "\\frac{1}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{4}{1}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionMultiplication.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_multiplicera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{1}{2} \\cdot \\frac{6}{3}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{0}{1}",
        "\\frac{11}{10}",
        "\\frac{5}{2}",
        "\\frac{1}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{1}{1}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionMultiplication.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_multiplicera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{8}{7} \\cdot \\frac{8}{7}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{689}{490}",
        "\\frac{1}{1}",
        "\\frac{64}{49}",
        "\\frac{16}{7}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{64}{49}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionMultiplication.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_multiplicera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{4}{6} \\cdot \\frac{1}{2}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{1}{3}",
        "\\frac{7}{6}",
        "\\frac{13}{30}",
        "\\frac{0}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{1}{3}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionMultiplication.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_multiplicera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{4}{8} \\cdot \\frac{2}{6}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{0}{1}",
        "\\frac{4}{15}",
        "\\frac{5}{6}",
        "\\frac{1}{6}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{1}{6}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionMultiplication.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_multiplicera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{5}{4} + \\frac{9}{1}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{41}{4}",
        "\\frac{45}{4}",
        "\\frac{207}{20}",
        "\\frac{10}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{41}{4}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionAddition.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_addera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{8}{2} + \\frac{1}{5}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{4}{5}",
        "\\frac{43}{10}",
        "\\frac{21}{5}",
        "\\frac{4}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{21}{5}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionAddition.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_addera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{8}{9} + \\frac{5}{2}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{2}{1}",
        "\\frac{61}{18}",
        "\\frac{157}{45}",
        "\\frac{20}{9}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{61}{18}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionAddition.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_addera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{8}{3} + \\frac{10}{9}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{3}{1}",
        "\\frac{349}{90}",
        "\\frac{80}{27}",
        "\\frac{102}{27}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{102}{27}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionAddition.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_addera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{6}{4} + \\frac{10}{5}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{18}{5}",
        "\\frac{3}{1}",
        "\\frac{7}{2}",
        "\\frac{7}{4}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{7}{2}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionAddition.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_addera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{3}{4} - \\frac{7}{6}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{-5}{12}",
        "\\frac{-31}{60}",
        "\\frac{-1}{1}",
        "\\frac{7}{8}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{-5}{12}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionSubtraction.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_subtrahera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{6}{10} - \\frac{4}{6}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{-1}{15}",
        "\\frac{2}{5}",
        "\\frac{-1}{6}",
        "\\frac{0}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{-1}{15}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionSubtraction.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_subtrahera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{2}{9} - \\frac{9}{3}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{-75}{27}",
        "\\frac{2}{3}",
        "\\frac{-259}{90}",
        "\\frac{-3}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{-75}{27}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionSubtraction.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_subtrahera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{7}{5} - \\frac{2}{8}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{21}{20}",
        "\\frac{23}{20}",
        "\\frac{7}{20}",
        "\\frac{1}{1}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{23}{20}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionSubtraction.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_subtrahera",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "subject": "kvantitativ",
      "category": "basics",
      "question": "\\frac{1}{9} - \\frac{8}{2}",
      "answers": [
        "\\frac{-35}{9}",
        "\\frac{-4}{1}",
        "\\frac{4}{9}",
        "\\frac{-359}{90}"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "\\frac{-35}{9}",
      "drawing": [],
      "explanation": "FractionSubtraction.mp4",
      "moment": "basics_fraktioner_subtrahera",
      "difficulty": 1
    }
  ]
}